López Fernando

Federal Police

email: FernandoFranciscoMatias@gmail.com

RESUME SUMMARY

For 13 years I have worked in the Argentine Federal Police. In said governmental institution. I have taken many defense and protection courses. I have also worked and participated in UN special peace operations. I have worked as a waiter in a salon for 4 years, I have experience in a cafeteria.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PFA (FEDERAL POLICE) CABA, Buenos Aires Argentina **Aeronautical Video and Communications Division**

Central (Restaurant) Villa Lugano, Buenos Aires Argentina **Jockey Club** (Party room and events) San Isidro, Buenos Aires Argentina

dro, Buenos Aires Argentina (2006-2010)

Date Started - Date Ended

(09/2012-10/2022)

Date Started - Date Ended

(2019/2021)

(02/2008-08/2012)

EDUCATION

ORT, CABA, Buenos Aires Argentina

Technique, programmer analyst, Certificate incomplete

Platzi, Bogota Colombia

Course, Certificate JAVA

Date Started – Date Ended
(06/2021-02/2022)

SKILLS

FEDERAL POLICE

- Systems Operator LEO3- Airbus EC135 & EC145
- VANT Operator.
- Presidential Custody
- tactics anti-terrorism
- Weapons handling

PROGRAMMER ANALYST

- JAVA
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL

OFFICE PROGRAMS

- Microsoft Office
- Adobe css6

ADDITIONAL SECTIONS

DRIVER'S LICENSE

Seguridad Vial, Vicente López, Buenos Aires

Categori: B2 D1 (professional)

Date License Was Issued
30 November 2021

Operator VANT and cabin crew

ANAC -CABA, Buenos Aires

Date Started – Date Ended 28 April 2016